Leo F. Solt papers, 1643-1996 C154
Indiana University Archives
Leo F. Solt papers
1643-1996
1940-1996
Indiana University Archives
Solt, Leo F. (Leo Frank), 1921-
C154
16.2 cubic feet 17 boxes
Leo F. Solt, professor emeritus of History and dean of the University Graduate School, taught at the University of Iowa and the University of Massachusetts before joining the Indiana University faculty in 1955. In 1978 he was named dean of the University Graduate School, a position he held until 1987. The collection consists of biographical records, research notes, correspondence, and lecture notes.
Access Restrictions
Select files are closed to researchers, including student papers and recommendation letters. Please consult the archivist for further information.
Biographical Note
Leo F. Solt, professor emeritus of History and dean of the University Graduate School, was born on October 12, 1921 in Waterloo, Iowa, and died in 1994 at the age of 72.
He received his B.A. in 1943 from Iowa State Teachers College (now the University of Northern Iowa), before joining the U.S. Navy in 1943 to serve as an officer on the aircraft carrier Bataan in the Pacific during the final years of World War II. Following the war, he attended graduate school, receiving his M.A. in 1948 from Iowa State University and his Ph.D. from Columbia University in 1955. Solt taught courses at the University of Iowa and the University of Massachusetts before joining the Indiana University faculty in 1955. He was promoted to full professor in 1961, accepted the responsibility of Acting Chair of Indiana University's Department of History from 1962-1963, and served as Chair of the Department of History from 1965-1970. He also chaired the West European Studies Program Committee. In 1978 he was named dean of the University Graduate School, a position he held until 1987. During his tenure in the department and the graduate school, he was instrumental in bringing the Journal of American History, the national office of the Organization of American Historians, and the American Historical Review to Indiana University. Solt retired in 1992 with the title Professor Emeritus of History.
Solt served as the president of the Midwest Conference on British Studies from 1968 to 1970 and as Vice President for Research of the American Historical Association in 1975. He is the author of two books Saints in Arms: Puritans and Democracy in Cromwell's Army and Church and State in Early Modern England, 1509-1640, as well as numerous reviews and scholarly articles, including "History of Britain, 1603-1714" for the 15th edition of the Encyclopedia Britannica.
Arrangement
Collection is organized into five series: Biographical material; Teaching files; Research and publications; Correspondence; and Subject files. The Biographical material series is further organized into two subseries: Education material and Subject files. The Research and papers series is also organized into two subseries: Published material and Manuscripts.
Scope and Content Note
The collection is organized into five series. The first series, Biographical material (1940-1996) consists of two sub-series: Education materials (1940-1956), and Subject files (1940-1996). The Education materials subseries contains files relating to Solt's studies at Iowa State Teachers College, Iowa State University and Columbia University. The Subject files contain Solt's personal materials such as clippings and artifacts from WWII, his vita, and awards received.
The second series is Teaching files (1947-1992), which contains class materials such as reading lists, lecture notes, and examination questions.
The Research and publications series (1941-1993) consists of two sub-series: Published material (1956-1993), and Manuscripts (1941-1990). Published material primarily consists of copies of Solt's articles published in various journals. Manuscripts contain rough and advanced drafts of Solt's published books, such as Church and State in Early Modern England, and Saints in Arms: Puritans and Democracy in Cromwell's Army, as well as manuscripts for numerous other articles and talks.
The fourth series, Correspondence (1941-1994) contains letters exchanged between Solt and his parents during WWII, correspondence with publishers, and other general correspondence with acquaintances. Correspondence related to Solt's activities in association with his roles at Indiana University, including communication with students and colleagues, is present as well; many of these files are restricted due to presence of sensitive student recommendations and discussions of academic performance.
Subject files (1643-1995, bulk 1944-1995), the final series, contains an extensive range of clippings, notes, topical documents, and reading lists related to Solt's research and professional activities. Many records relate to American and European history topics relevant to Solt's teaching and research. Of particular interest is an original manuscript of a seventeenth century sermon. Also included in this series are files relating to Solt's involvement with organizations within as well as outside of Indiana University (e.g. Bloomington Faculty Council, American Historical Association, Midwest Conference on British Studies). Other files in the series document Solt's involvement with study abroad programs, research and sabbatical trips, committees, and grants pursued.
Restricted files are listed where they would fall intellectually but are physically stored at the end of the collection.
Related Material
See the following collections for Leo F. Solt's files in association with his other professional roles at Indiana University: C155: Indiana University Dept. of History Chair's records and C156: Indiana University Graduate School Dean's records.
Acquisition Information
Accession numbers 0183, 96/019, 99/050, 2009/001, 2013/091.
Appraisal
Duplicate files with the same content have been merged. Course evaluations were discarded.
Hisorians --Indiana --Bloomington.; History teachers --Indiana --Bloomington.; History --Study and teaching (Higher) --Indiana.; Church and state --England --History --16th century.; Church and state --England --History --17th century.; England --Church History --16th century.; England --Church History --17th century.; Great Britain --History --Civil War, 1642-1649.; Christianity and politics --Great Britain --History --17th century.; Chaplains, Military --Great Britain --History --17th century.; Puritans --England --History --17th century.; Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658; Indiana University. Department of History; Indiana University, Bloomington. Department of History; Indiana University. Graduate School; Indiana University, Bloomington. Graduate School; Great Britain. Army -- History -- 17th century; Solt, Leo F. (Leo Frank), 1921- -- Church and state in early modern England, 1509-1640; Solt, Leo F. (Leo Frank), 1921- -- Saints in arms
- Biographical Material, 1940-1996, undated (Box 1)
  - Education Materials, 1940-1956, undated (Box 1)
    - Advanced Studies and Research, undated (Box 1)
    - Columbia Commencement, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Course Materials (Box 1)
      - Anglo-Saxon Divisions, undated (Box 1)
      - Appreciation of Literature, 1941 (Box 1)
      - Bibliographies, 1949-1950, undated (Box 1)
      - Bibliography of New England Calvinism, 1947 (Box 1)
      - Classical Economists, undated (Box 1)
      - Correspondence, Gerald Strauss Distinguished Professor Nomination, undated (Box 1)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Restricted
      - English Constitutional History, 1950 (Box 1)
      - English Historians, undated (Box 1)
      - English Literature, 1940 (Box 1)
      - Europe in Transition, undated (Box 1)
      - Europe since 1870, 1941 (Box 1)
      - Europe since 1918, undated (Box 1)
      - European Cultural History, 19th century, undated (Box 1)
      - European Diplomacy, undated (Box 1)
      - Exams, 1947 (Box 1)
      - French Revolution and Napoleon, undated (Box 1)
      - History Materials (Box 1)
        - 1950 (Box 1)
        - 1950-1951 (Box 1)
        - 1952, undated (Box 1)
        - undated, (3 folders) (Box 1)
      - Letters of Recommendation (Box 1)
        - 1956-1960 (Box 1)
        - 1961-1965 (Box 1)
        - 1988-1990 (Box 1)
      - Magazine Pictures, 1950 (Box 1)
      - Milton and Calvin, undated (Box 1)
      - Milton and His Contemporaries, undated (Box 1)
      - Northern Reformation (Calvin), undated (Box 1)
      - Outline and Sources for a History of Western Civilization, 1947 (Box 1)
      - Philosophies of History, undated (Box 1)
      - Philosophy, 1951 (Box 1)
      - Social and Economic History of the United States, undated (Box 1)
      - Student Papers, 1947 (Box 1)
      - Tillich- Church History, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Dissertation (Box 1)
      - Abstract, 1953 (Box 1)
      - Defense, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Notes for Thesis, undated (Box 1)
  - Subject Files, 1940-1996, undated (Box 1)
    - American Legion Navy Cap from WWII, undated (Box 1)
    - Artifacts collected by Leo Solt from Bataan, undated (Box 1)
    - Awards (Received) (Box 1)
      - In Appreciation for Contributions to College of Arts and Science /Graduate School – Alumni Association, 1987 (Box 1)
      - Phantom Canon Road Expedition Award, 1987 (Box 1)
      - The Society of Professional JournalistsRocking Chair Award, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Book Donation, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Clippings 1993-1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1960-1991 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum Vitae (C.V.) and Related Materials, Leo Solt, 1972-1980 (Box 1)
    - Description and Narration, Leo Solt creative writing, 1940 (Box 1)
    - England Trip, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Graduate Perspectives, the Graduate Alumni Newsletter, Obituary, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
    - Harvard Business School, Death Announcement, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Harvard Midshipmen-Officers Classes - 40th Reunion, June 26-29, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Identification and Membership Cards, undated (Box 2)
    - Indiana Alumni Announcements, Solt's obituary, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Leo Solt Distinguished Service Award, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Leo Solt Dissertation Travel Award, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
    - Manuscripts, Bataan, undated (Box 2)
    - Memorial and Funeral Service, 1993-1995 (Box 2)
    - Memorial Resolution, Bloomington Faculty Council, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Memorial Tree, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Navy Reunion, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Phi Alpha Theta, 1955, undated (Box 2)
    - Retiring Faculty program, Leo Solt, 1992 (Box 2)
    - Tree Planting in the Memory of Leo F. Solt, 1995 (Box 2)
    - U.S.S. Bataan (Box 2)
      - Journal Entries, 1945 (Box 2)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1945 (Box 2)
      - Yearbook, 1 August 1943 - 17 October 1945 (Box 2)
    - Leo Solt's Will (Box 2)
      - 1985 (Box 2)
      - Draft Copy, 1994 (Box 2)
      - Living Will, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
    - Who's Who in America, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - World War II Newspaper Clippings, 1944-1945; (2 folders) (Box 2)
- Teaching files, 1947-1992, undated (Box 2)
  - Audio Visual Course Materials, 1968-1974 (Box 2)
  - B372 English Constitutional History (Box 2)
    - Assignment sheets, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Exams, undated; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Final examination, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Materials, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Notes, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
      - undated (Box 2)
      - Spring, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Course Journals (Box 2)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - 1972 (Box 2)
  - Early Modern English History - Reading List, undated (Box 2)
  - European Maps, undated (Box 2)
  - H103 European History, undated (Box 2)
  - H103 - History of Western Civilization - Assignment Sheets, undated (Box 2)
  - H209 English History I (Box 2)
    - Assignment sheets, 1970-1973; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Final Examination (Box 2)
      - 1966-1983 (Box 2)
      - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - General (Box 3)
      - 1972-1979 (Box 3)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 3)
    - Materials (Box 3)
      - 1981-1988 (Box 3)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - Undated (Box 3)
      - 1972 (Box 3)
      - Other, 1984-1987 (Box 3)
      - Sheets, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Slides, 1973 (Box 3)
      - Tests, 1976-1980 (Box 3)
  - H210 English History I (Box 3)
    - Assignment sheets, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Exams, 1967-1971 (Box 3)
    - Final examination, 1967 (Box 3)
  - H217 The Nature of History (Box 3)
    - Assignment sheets, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Assignment Sheets and Exams, undated (Box 3)
    - Attendance and Introduction, undated (Box 3)
    - Exams, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - Problems, undated (Box 3)
    - Short Paper, undated (Box 3)
  - H225 Special Topics - The Nature of History for Teachers (Box 3)
    - Course description, undated (Box 3)
    - Report, 1972 (Box 3)
  - H303-304 European History, 1960 (Box 3)
  - H308 English History (Box 3)
    - Assignments, undated (Box 3)
    - Assignment sheets, 1953-1961 (Box 3)
    - Exams, 1955-1963 (Box 3)
    - Final examinations, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1971 (Box 3)
  - H309 English History (Box 3)
    - Assignment sheets, undated (Box 3)
    - Final examinations, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3)
  - H331 Honors Seminar in Historiography, undated (Box 3)
  - H425 Reformation in England and Scotland, 1974 (Box 3)
  - H501 Introduction to the Professional Study of History, 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - H503-504 Stuart and Tudor England (Box 3)
    - Assignment sheets, 1954-1955 (Box 3)
    - Exams, 1966 (Box 3)
    - Final examinations, 1966 (Box 3)
  - H507-508 Augustan England (Box 3)
    - Exams, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Final examinations, undated (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3)
  - H513 Victorian England, undated (Box 3)
  - H514 Contemporary English History, 1958 (Box 3)
  - H529 Puritanism in Early America, undated (Box 3)
  - H630 English History Colloquium (Box 3)
    - Bibliographies (Box 3)
      - Undated (Box 3)
      - 1973 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - 1970 (Box 3)
      - 1973 (Box 4)
      - 1978 (Box 4)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 4)
      - Spring, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
      - 1989-1992 (Box 4)
    - Reading Lists (Box 4)
      - 1967-1970 (Box 4)
      - 1970 (Box 4)
      - 1971 (Box 4)
  - H847 Seminar in English History, 1961-1969 (Box 4)
  - History 5 - European History before 1915, Exams, 1952-1955 (Box 4)
  - History 5 and 6 (Box 4)
    - Assignments, 1951-1956 (Box 4)
    - Mapwork, undated (Box 4)
  - History 6 Exams, 1954-1956 (Box 4)
  - History 31 - English History to 1689 (Box 4)
    - Exams, 1953-1954 (Box 4)
    - Materials, 1953-1955 (Box 4)
  - History 32 Exams, 1953-1955 (Box 4)
  - History Class Material (Box 4)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 4)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Intensive Freshman Seminar, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - IUPUI Class, 1987-1989 (Box 4)
  - J481 Historiography, undated (Box 4)
  - K491 Seminar in Historiography, 1964-1975 (Box 4)
  - Library Reading Lists, undated (Box 4)
  - Maps of England, undated (Box 4)
  - Political Thought, Seminar course, undated (Box 4)
  - S830 English History Seminar, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Student Papers (Box 4)
    - Miller, James E. – "Rex versus Bertrand Russell 1914-1918," M.A. Thesis, 1991 (Box 4)
    - 1964, undated (Box 4)
    - 1964-1978 (Box 4)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 4)
  - Transparencies, undated (Box 4a)
  - Western Civilization, 1947-1948 (Box 4a)
- Research and Papers, 1941-1993, undated
  - Published Material, 1956-1993, undated (Box 4a)
    - Anti-Intellectualism in Puritan Revolution, 1956 (Box 4a)
    - Britain and Ireland History, Encyclopedia Britannica, 15th ed., 1974 (Box 4a)
    - John Saltmarch: New Model Army Chaplain, undated (Box 4a)
    - The New Model Army in England, Ireland and Scotland, 1645-1653, by Ian Gentles - Review, 1993 (Box 4a)
    - Protestant Mind of the English Reformation by Charles & Katherine George, Review, undated (Box 4a)
    - Puritanism and Democracy in the New Model Army, 1959 (Box 4a)
    - Puritanism, Capitalism, Democracy, and the New Science, 1967 (Box 4a)
    - Revolutionary Calvinist Parties in England under Elizabeth I and Charles I, 1958 (Box 4a)
    - Some Reflections Upon the Study of English History, 1957 (Box 4a)
    - What Was Cromwell's Religion, 1958 (Box 4a)
    - William Dell: New Model Army Chaplain, undated (Box 4a)
    - Winstanley, Lilburne, and the Case of John Fielder, undated (Box 4a)
  - Manuscripts, 1941-1990, undated (Box 4a)
    - Articles Accepted, 1956-1960 (Box 4a)
    - Article Review, James Hitchcock, 1971 (Box 4a)
    - Biographical Dictionary of English Radicals in the Seventeenth Century, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
    - Book Reviews (Box 5)
      - 1956-1972 (Box 5)
      - 1970-1990 (Box 5)
    - Capp, Book Review, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Challenge of Gregorgianism, undated (Box 5)
    - Chicago Press, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Church and State Materials, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Church and State Project, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
    - Church and State Speech, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Church and State Talk, undated (Box 5)
    - Church and State, undated (Box 5)
    - Church and State, (original), undated (Box 5)
    - Church and State in Early Modern England (Box 5)
      - Rough draft with notes (Box 5)
        - Introduction, undated (Box 5)
        - Chapter 1, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
        - Chapter 2, undated; (3 folders) (Box 5)
        - Chapter 3, 1976, undated; (2 folders) (Box 5)
        - Chapter 4, 1976, undated; (4 folders) (Box 5)
        - Chapter 5, 1978, undated; (folders 1-2 of 4) (Box 5)
        - Chapter 5, 1978, undated; (folders 3-4 of 4) (Box 6)
      - General comments, undated (Box 6)
      - Typed draft with corrections (Box 6)
        - Chapter 1, 1987 (Box 6)
        - Chapter 2, 1987 (Box 6)
        - Chapter 3, 1987 (Box 6)
        - Chapter 4, 1987 (Box 6)
        - Chapter 5, 1987-1990 (Box 6)
        - Conclusion, 1987 (Box 6)
      - Typed draft without corrections, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 6)
      - Spiral bound notebooks (Box 6)
        - Chapters 1-2, undated (Box 6)
        - Chapters 3-4, undated (Box 6)
        - Chapter 5-Bibliography, undated (Box 6)
      - Galley prints, 1989; (2 folders) (Box 6)
      - 26 Computer floppy disks (size 5 ¼ inch) organized by chapter, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
    - English Revolution Talk, undated (Box 6)
    - Films in English History Talk, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Forston, 1959-1960 (Box 6)
    - "History of Indiana University" talk, 1990 (Box 6)
    - "How Does a Historian Learn?", undated (Box 6)
    - How the Views of Historians Have Changed: a Study of Left-Wing movements in the Puritan Revolution, 1948 (Box 6)
    - John L. Lewis Samson of Labor, 1941 (Box 6)
    - The Lesson of History and Vietnam, Paul B. Cook, West Kentucky State College, undated (Box 6)
    - Manuscripts Reviewed by Dean Solt, 1984-1988 (Box 6)
    - Manuscripts Submitted: Revolutionary Calvinist Parties in England under Elizabeth I and Charles I, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Muggletonians Book Review, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Observations Concerning "The Agricola of Tacitus," student paper by Andrew Clark Graham, undated (Box 6)
    - Poland Paper, Church and State, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Poland Speech, Church and State, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Polish Conference Paper "English Antecedents of the American Constitution: Church and State", Warsaw, Poland, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Political Obedience in Tudor England, undated (Box 7)
    - Princeton University Press, undated (Box 7)
    - "Religion and Politics Under the Tudors and Stuarts," talk by Leo Solt, undated (Box 7)
    - Renaissance Seminar, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Review of Laurence's "Parliamentary Army Chaplains", undated (Box 7)
    - Saints in Arms (Box 7)
      - Research materials, 1952-1958 (Box 7)
      - Notebooks, undated (Box 7)
      - Notes, undated; (7 folders) (Box 7)
      - Rough draft with notes (Box 7)
        - Introduction, undated; (2 folders) (Box 7)
        - Chapter 1, undated; (3 folders) (Box 7)
        - Chapter 2, undated (Box 8)
        - Chapter 3, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8)
        - Chapter 4, undated; (4 folders) (Box 8)
        - Chapter 5, undated (Box 8)
        - Chapter 6, undated (Box 8)
        - Chapter 7, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8)
        - Chapter 8, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8)
        - Chapter 9, undated (Box 8)
        - Chapter 10, undated (Box 8)
      - Typed rough manuscript (Box 8)
        - 1959-1961 (Box 8)
        - undated (Box 8)
      - Typed manuscript, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Reviews of Saints, 1959-1960 (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960-1969 (Box 9)
    - Science and History, 1948 (Box 9)
    - The Widening Gate: Bristol and the Atlantic Economy, 1450-1700, by David Sacks, Review, undated (Box 9)
    - Winstanley, Lilburne, and the Case of John Fielder (Box 9)
      - Copy of Petition, 1978-1981 (Box 9)
      - Drafts (Box 9)
        - 1978-1981 (Box 9)
        - undated (Box 9)
      - Research Material, 1978-1981 (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9)
- Correspondence, 1941-1994, undated (Box 9)
  - General (Box 9)
    - 1956-1958, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1959-1960, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1961, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1962, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1963 (Box 9)
    - 1964, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1965, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1966 (Box 9)
    - 1967 (Box 10)
    - 1968 (Box 10)
    - 1969 (Box 10)
    - 1970, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - 1971 (Box 10)
    - 1972 (Box 10)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 10)
    - 1973-1979 (Box 10)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 10)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - 1979-1982 (Box 10)
    - 1982 (Box 10)
    - 1983-1989 (Box 10)
    - 1984-1989 (Box 10)
    - 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - A, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    Restricted records removed
  - Allen, Paul, 1973 (Box 10)
  - B, 1969-1973 (Box 10)
  - Backus, Susan, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Baepler, Richard, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Baker, Donald E., 1973 (Box 10)
  - Barrows, Robert, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Berry, Boyd, 1969-1973 (Box 10)
  - Bodenhamer, David, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - Booker, Roger, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Boris, Edna, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Boyd, Willis D., 1972 (Box 10)
  - Bozell, Douglas A., 1989 (Box 10)
  - Burell, Sidney A., 1963-1975 (Box 10)
  - Burgess Publishing Company, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Burlakoff, Sheridan (Mrs.), 1972-1978 (Box 10)
  - C, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
  - Cards and Invitations, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - Chaska, Norma, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
  - Clark, Andrew, Library, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
  - Clouse, Robert (Box 10)
    - 1970-1975 (Box 10)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 10)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 10)
  - Collins, Naomi (Mrs.), 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Cook, J.F.D., 1941 (Box 10)
  - Cridland, Nancy, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Cuffel, Victoria, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
  - Curriculum Vitae (C.V.) Information, 1968-1970 (Box 10)
  - D, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
  - Daynes, Kathryn, 1974-1976 (Box 10)
  - E, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - F, 1967-1973 (Box 10)
  - Farrar, Robert, 1970-1973 (Box 10)
  - Ferguson, Jim, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Fish, Lydia, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Flaningham, John R., 1972-1977 (Box 10)
  - Freyer, Tony, 1973 (Box 10)
  - G, 1971-1973 (Box 10)
  - Gardner, James, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Gonso, Harry, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Grabau, Thomas W., 1970-1973 (Box 10)
  - Graham, Andy, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Greaves, R., 1970-1989 (Box 10)
  - H, 1970-1974 (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Emily, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Hamerow, Theodore, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Hanak, Walter, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
  - Hartman, Marilyn, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
  - Harvester Press, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Havran, Martin J., 1972; 1987-1989 (Box 11)
  - Hawkins, Tom, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Herwig, Holger, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Hiner, Donald, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - The Historian, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Howard, Thomas, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Hughes, Pam, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Huntington Library, 1982-1989 (Box 11)
  - I, 1969-1973 (Box 11)
  - Illing, Peter, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Indiana University Job negotiations, 1954 (Box 11)
  - J, 1970-1973 (Box 11)
  - Jacobs, Bernice, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
  - James, Boyd, 1972 (Box 11)